[
  {
    "question": "Which letter comes after 'B'?",
    "choices": [
      "A",
      "C",
      "D",
      "E"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "category": "Letters",
    "versions": [
      "Which letter comes after 'B'?",
      "What letter follows the letter 'B' in alphabetic order?",
      "What letter follows the letter 'B'?",
      "What is the following letter of the letter 'B'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه حرف تأتي بعد حرف \"ب\"؟",
      "ما هي الحرف التالية للحرف \"ب\" بالترتيب الأبجدي؟",
      "ما هي الحرف التالية للحرف \"ب\"؟",
      "ما هي الحرف التالية للحرف \"ب\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "A A",
      "م ج",
      "د/",
      "E E"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "م ج",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first letter of the word 'Apple'?",
    "choices": [
      "A",
      "P",
      "E",
      "L"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "category": "Letters",
    "versions": [
      "What is the first letter of the word 'Apple'?",
      "What is the initial character of the word 'Apple'?",
      "What is the opening letter of the word 'Apple'?",
      "What is the initial letter of the word 'Apple'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الحرف الأول لكلمة \"إبل\"؟",
      "ما هي الشخصية الأولية لكلمة \"أبل\"؟",
      "ما هي الحرف الافتتاحية لكلمة \"إبل\"؟",
      "ما هو الحرف الأولي لكلمة \"إبل\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "A A",
      "م ف ف",
      "E E",
      "L"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "A A",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which word starts with the letter 'D'?",
    "choices": [
      "Car",
      "Dog",
      "Apple",
      "Sun"
    ],
    "answer": "Dog",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "Which word starts with the letter 'D'?",
      "What is a word that starts with the letter 'D'?",
      "What is the word that starts with the letter 'D'?",
      "What word starts with the letter 'D'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه كلمة تبدأ بالحرف \"د\"؟",
      "ما هي الكلمة اللي تبدأ بالحرف \"د\"؟",
      "ما هي الكلمة اللي تبدأ بالحرف \"د\"؟",
      "ما الكلمة اللي تبدأ بالحرف \"د\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "سيارة",
      "",
      "",
      "صنس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the missing word? 'The cat is ____ the box.'",
    "choices": [
      "in",
      "on",
      "under",
      "at"
    ],
    "answer": "in",
    "category": "Sentences",
    "versions": [
      "What is the missing word? 'The cat is ____ the box.'",
      "What is the missing word in this sentence? 'The cat is ____ the box.",
      "What is the missing word? 'The cat is ____ the box.",
      "What is the missing letter? 'The cat is ____ the box."
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هي الكلمة المفقودة؟ القطة هي الصندوق",
      "ما هي الكلمة الناقصة في هذه الجُمله؟ 'القط هو _ الصندوق.",
      "ما هي الكلمة المفقودة؟ القطة هي الصندوق.",
      "ما هي الحرف المفقودة؟ القطة هي الصندوق."
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في",
      "بما في ده",
      "ق",
      "مجلس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "في",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is a complete sentence?",
    "choices": [
      "Running fast",
      "The boy runs",
      "Very happy",
      "In the school"
    ],
    "answer": "The boy runs",
    "category": "Sentences",
    "versions": [
      "Which of these is a complete sentence?",
      "Which one of these sentences is a complete one?",
      "Which of the following is a sentence that is complete?",
      "Which of the following is a complete sentence?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه من هذه هي الجُمله الكاملة؟",
      "إيه واحد من هذه الجمل هو واحد كامل؟",
      "إيه من ما يلي هو الجُمله الكاملة؟",
      "إيه من التالي هو الجُمله الكاملة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "يجري بسرعة",
      "الولد يركض",
      "سعيد جداً",
      "في المدرسة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الولد يركض",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which word does not belong?",
    "choices": [
      "Apple",
      "Banana",
      "Chair",
      "Orange"
    ],
    "answer": "Chair",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "Which word does not belong?",
      "What is an untruthful word?",
      "What is a word that is not suitable?",
      "Which word is not a valid option?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه كلمة لا تنتمي؟",
      "ما هي كلمة غير حقيقية؟",
      "ما هي الكلمة غير المناسبة ؟",
      "إيه كلمة ليست خياراً صحيحاً؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "",
      "",
      "الرئيس",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الرئيس",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence:",
    "choices": [
      "I like play",
      "I playing",
      "I like to play",
      "Like I play"
    ],
    "answer": "I like to play",
    "category": "Sentences",
    "versions": [
      "Choose the correct sentence:",
      "Which sentence is correct?",
      "What is the appropriate sentence?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "انتقِ:",
      "ما هي الجُمله الصحيحة؟",
      "ما هي الجُمله المناسبة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "أحب اللعب",
      "أنا ألعب",
      "أحب أن ألعب",
      "مثل ما ألعب"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "أحب أن ألعب",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the opposite of 'hot'?",
    "choices": [
      "cold",
      "warm",
      "fire",
      "heat"
    ],
    "answer": "cold",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "What is the opposite of 'hot'?",
      "What is the antonym of 'hot'?",
      "What is the opposite meaning of 'hot'?",
      "What is the reverse meaning of 'hot'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو عكس \"الإثارة\"؟",
      "ما هو اسم \"هوت\"؟",
      "ما هو المعنى المقابل لـ \"هوت\"؟",
      "ما هو المعنى العكسي لـ \"هوت\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "*..",
      "مــن",
      "إطلاق نار",
      "درجة الحرارة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "*..",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is a verb?",
    "choices": [
      "Run",
      "Blue",
      "Chair",
      "Apple"
    ],
    "answer": "Run",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "Which one is a verb?",
      "What is a verb?",
      "What is a noun?",
      "What is a form of a verb?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه واحد هو الفعل؟",
      "ما هو الفعل؟",
      "ما هو العبد؟",
      "ما هو شكل الفعل؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "تنفيذ تنفيذ",
      "طائرة من طراز LCS",
      "الرئيس",
      ""
    ],
    "answer_ar": "تنفيذ تنفيذ",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the plural of 'cat'?",
    "choices": [
      "Cats",
      "Cated",
      "Cat",
      "Cattes"
    ],
    "answer": "Cats",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "What is the plural of 'cat'?",
      "Can you tell me the plural of 'cat'?",
      "What is the plural of the word 'cat'?",
      "What is the plural form of the word 'cat'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الجمع بين \"كات\"؟",
      "هل يمكنك أن تخبرني بصيغة \"كات\"؟",
      "ما هو الجمع بين كلمة \"كات\"؟",
      "ما هو شكل الجمع لكلمة \"كات\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "",
      "المُنْطِكَة",
      "كات",
      "سِِِِ كِِِِ سِِِ"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct article: ___ apple",
    "choices": [
      "A",
      "An",
      "The",
      "Some"
    ],
    "answer": "An",
    "category": "Sentences",
    "versions": [
      "Choose the correct article: ___ apple",
      "What is the appropriate choice: __ apple?",
      "What is the right choice: apple ___?",
      "Which article is appropriate: __ apple?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "اختر المقالة الصحيحة: _ تفاح",
      "ما هو الخيار المناسب: _ تفاح؟",
      "ما هو الخيار الصحيح: تفاح _؟",
      "ما هي المادة المناسبة: _ تفاح؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "A A",
      "A",
      "الـ",
      "بعض"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "A",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the last letter in 'Dog'?",
    "choices": [
      "D",
      "G",
      "O",
      "T"
    ],
    "answer": "G",
    "category": "Letters",
    "versions": [
      "What is the last letter in 'Dog'?",
      "What is the ending pronoun used in the title 'Dog'?",
      "What is the concluding letter of 'Dog'?",
      "What is the letter that completes 'Dog'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الحرف الأخير في \"الكلب\"؟",
      "ما هو البيان النهائي المستخدم في العنوان 'الكلب'؟",
      "ما هي الحرف الختامية من \"الكلب\"؟",
      "ما هي الحرف اللي تكمل \"الكلب\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "د/",
      "",
      "مان",
      "ألف"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence describes a happy feeling?",
    "choices": [
      "She is crying",
      "He is jumping with joy",
      "They are sad",
      "The dog is barking"
    ],
    "answer": "He is jumping with joy",
    "category": "Comprehension",
    "versions": [
      "Which sentence describes a happy feeling?",
      "What is the word that characterizes a positive feeling?",
      "What is the word that characterizes a feeling of joy and happiness?",
      "What is the word that characterizes a feeling of joy?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه جُمله تصف شعوراً سعيداً؟",
      "ما هي الكلمة اللي تصف شعورا ايجابيا ؟",
      "ما هي الكلمة اللي تميز الشعور بالفرح والسعادة ؟",
      "ما هي الكلمة اللي تصف شعورا بالفرح ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "إنها تبكي",
      "هو يقفز بفرح",
      "هم يَحْزونَ",
      "الكلب ينبح"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "هو يقفز بفرح",
    "category_ar": "عدد"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you do with a book?",
    "choices": [
      "Eat",
      "Read",
      "Throw",
      "Sit"
    ],
    "answer": "Read",
    "category": "Comprehension",
    "versions": [
      "What do you do with a book?",
      "What do you typically do with a book?",
      "How do you utilize a book?",
      "What is your approach to using a book?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ماذا تفعل بكتاب؟",
      "ما الذي تفعله عادة بكتاب؟",
      "كيف تستخدم كتاب؟",
      "ما هو نهجك في استخدام كتاب ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "كل من كل كلكل",
      "re rech",
      "(القاء)",
      "الجلوس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "re rech",
    "category_ar": "عدد"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence is about food?",
    "choices": [
      "The bird flies",
      "He eats pizza",
      "The sky is blue",
      "They run fast"
    ],
    "answer": "He eats pizza",
    "category": "Comprehension",
    "versions": [
      "Which sentence is about food?",
      "What sentence pertains to the topic of food?",
      "What is the food related sentence?",
      "What is the food-related sentence?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه جُمله هي عن الطعام؟",
      "ما هي الجُمله اللي تتعلق بموضوع الغذاء؟",
      "ما هي الجُمله المتعلقة بالطعام؟",
      "ما هو الحكم المتعلق بالغذاء؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الطيران",
      "إنه يأكل البيتزا",
      "السماء زرقاء",
      "يركضون مسرعين"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "إنه يأكل البيتزا",
    "category_ar": "عدد"
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the question sentence:",
    "choices": [
      "He likes apples",
      "Do you like apples?",
      "Apples are tasty",
      "I eat apples"
    ],
    "answer": "Do you like apples?",
    "category": "Sentences",
    "versions": [
      "Find the question sentence:",
      "Find the question sentence?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "اوجد جُمله السؤال:",
      "هل وجدت جُمله السؤال؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "يحبّ تفاح",
      "هل تحب التفاح؟",
      "تُؤجج المُسَتَع",
      "أنا آكل تفاح"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "هل تحب التفاح؟",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these words is a color?",
    "choices": [
      "Run",
      "Blue",
      "Eat",
      "Happy"
    ],
    "answer": "Blue",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "Which of these words is a color?",
      "What is the name of the color in these words?",
      "What is the name of the color in this word?",
      "Which one of these words is a shade?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه من هذه الكلمات هو لون؟",
      "ما هو اسم اللون في هذه الكلمات؟",
      "ما هو اسم اللون في هذه الكلمة؟",
      "إيه واحدة من هذه الكلمات هي الظل؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "تنفيذ تنفيذ",
      "طائرة من طراز LCS",
      "كل من كل كلكل",
      "سعيد سعيد"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "طائرة من طراز LCS",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is a question word?",
    "choices": [
      "Why",
      "Book",
      "Chair",
      "Dog"
    ],
    "answer": "Why",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "Which one is a question word?",
      "What is the name of a word used in asking questions?",
      "What is a word that can be used as a prompt?",
      "What is the name of a word used to ask questions?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيههما كلمة سؤال؟",
      "ما هو اسم الكلمة المستخدمة في طرح الأسئلة؟",
      "ما هي الكلمة اللي يمكن استخدامها كمسرِّع ؟",
      "ما هو اسم الكلمة المستخدمة لطرح الأسئلة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "ألف -",
      "كتاب",
      "الرئيس",
      ""
    ],
    "answer_ar": "ألف -",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you do at night?",
    "choices": [
      "Eat breakfast",
      "Sleep",
      "Go to school",
      "Play in sun"
    ],
    "answer": "Sleep",
    "category": "Comprehension",
    "versions": [
      "What do you do at night?",
      "What activities do you engage in during the evening?",
      "What activities do you engage in during the evening hours?",
      "What activities do you engage in during the night?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ماذا تفعل في الليل؟",
      "ما الأنشطة اللي تقوم بها أثناء المساء؟",
      "ما الأنشطة اللي تقوم بها أثناء ساعات المساء؟",
      "ما الأنشطة اللي تقوم بها أثناء الليل؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "",
      "النوم",
      "الذهاب إلى المدرسة",
      "اللعب في الشمس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "النوم",
    "category_ar": "عدد"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sentence tells about the weather?",
    "choices": [
      "It is raining",
      "He runs fast",
      "She is happy",
      "They eat apples"
    ],
    "answer": "It is raining",
    "category": "Comprehension",
    "versions": [
      "Which sentence tells about the weather?",
      "What is an example of a sentence that talks about the weather?",
      "Can you construct a sentence that describes the weather?",
      "What is a sentence that describes the weather?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما الجُمله اللي تقول عن الطقس؟",
      "ما هو مثال لجُمله تتحدث عن الطقس؟",
      "هل يمكنك بناء جُمله تصف الطقس؟",
      "ما هي الجُمله اللي تصف الطقس؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "هو يَمْسُ مطر",
      "يركض مسرعاً",
      "هي سعيدة",
      "يَأْكلونَ"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "هو يَمْسُ مطر",
    "category_ar": "عدد"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 + 5?",
    "choices": [
      "13",
      "12",
      "11",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "12",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 7 + 5?",
      "What is the result of adding 5 to the total of 7?",
      "What is the sum of 7 and 5?",
      "What is the result of adding 7 and 5?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو 7 + 5؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة إضافة 5 إلى المجموع 7؟",
      "ما هو مجموع 7 و 5؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة إضافة 7 و5؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "13",
      "",
      "",
      "٤١"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much is 18 - 9?",
    "choices": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "9",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "How much is 18 - 9?",
      "What is the result of subtracting 9 from 18?",
      "What is the sum of 18 and 9?",
      "What is the value of 18 raised to the 9th power?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "كم هو 18-9؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة طرح 9 من 18؟",
      "ما هو مجموع 18 و 9؟",
      "ما هي قيمة 18 مرفوعة للقوة التاسعة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "::",
      "8 8",
      "٠١",
      "7 7"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "::",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 x 4?",
    "choices": [
      "12",
      "16",
      "14",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 4 x 4?",
      "What is the outcome of 4 multiplied by itself?",
      "What is the answer to 4 multiplied by 4?",
      "What is the result of 4 multiplied by itself?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو 4x4؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة 4 مضروبة في نفسها؟",
      "ما هو الاجابة لـ 4 × 4؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة 4 مضروبة في نفسها؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "",
      "١٦",
      "٤١",
      "١٨"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "١٦",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 20 ÷ 5?",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 20 ÷ 5?",
      "What is the result of multiplying 20 by 5?",
      "What is the result of multiplying 20 and 5?",
      "What is the value of 20 to the power of 5?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو 20^5؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة ضرب 20 في 5؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة ضرب 20 و 5؟",
      "ما هي قيمة 20^5؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "3 3",
      "5 و 5",
      "٤",
      "6 6"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "٤",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 + 9?",
    "choices": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "15",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 6 + 9?",
      "What is the sum of 6 and 9?",
      "What is the result of adding 6 and 9?",
      "What is the total of 6 and 9?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو 6+9؟",
      "ما هو مجموع 6 و9؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة إضافة 6 و9؟",
      "ما هو مجموع 6 و 9؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "٤١",
      "١٥",
      "١٦",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "١٥",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much is 10 - 7?",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "3",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "How much is 10 - 7?",
      "What is the answer to 10 multiplied by 7?",
      "What is the total of 10 and 7?",
      "What is the numerical worth of 10 to 7?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "كم هو 10-7؟",
      "ما هو الاجابة لـ 10 مضروبة في 7؟",
      "ما هو المجموع 10 و 7؟",
      "ما هي القيمة العددية لـ 10 إلى 7؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "فريقان",
      "3 3",
      "٤",
      "5 و 5"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "3 3",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 x 3?",
    "choices": [
      "15",
      "12",
      "10",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "15",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 5 x 3?",
      "What is the result of multiplying 5 and 3?",
      "What is the result of multiplying 5 and then adding 2/3?",
      "What is the outcome of multiplying 5 and 3?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو 5x3؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة ضرب 5 و 3؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة ضرب 5 ومن ثم إضافة 2/3؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة ضرب 5 و 3؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "١٥",
      "",
      "٠١",
      "١٨"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "١٥",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 ÷ 4?",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 16 ÷ 4?",
      "What is the answer when 16 is divided by 4?",
      "What is the answer when 16 is multiplied by 4?",
      "What is the square root of 16?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو 16/4؟",
      "ما هو الاجابة عندما 16 مقسومة على 4؟",
      "ما هو الاجابة عندما تكون 16 مضروبة في 4؟",
      "ما هو الجذر التربيعي لـ 16؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "فريقان",
      "3 3",
      "٤",
      "5 و 5"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "٤",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 8?",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "10",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 2 + 8?",
      "What is the result of adding 2 and 8?",
      "What is the solution to 2 plus 8?",
      "What is the sum of 2 and 8?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو 2 + 8؟",
      "ما هي نتيجة إضافة 2 و8؟",
      "ما هو الحل لـ 2 + 8؟",
      "ما هو مجموع 2 و8؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "٠١",
      "",
      "::",
      "8 8"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "٠١",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 x 1?",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "9",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 9 x 1?",
      "What is the value of 9 multiplied by 1?",
      "What is the solution to 9 multiplied by 1?",
      "What is the result of multiplying 1 by 9?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو 9x1؟",
      "ما هي قيمة 9 مضروبة في 1؟",
      "ما هو الحل لـ 9 مضروبة في 1",
      "ما هي نتيجة ضرب 1×9؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "8 8",
      "::",
      "٠١",
      "7 7"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "::",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },
  {
    "question": "When do you eat breakfast?",
    "choices": [
      "At night",
      "In the morning",
      "In the evening",
      "Before bed"
    ],
    "answer": "In the morning",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "When do you eat breakfast?",
      "What time do you usually have breakfast?",
      "At what time do you usually have breakfast?",
      "When do you usually have your morning meal?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "متى تتناول إفطارك؟",
      "ما الوقت الذي عادة ما يكون لديك إفطار؟",
      "في إيه وقت تتناولين الفطور عادةً؟",
      "متى لديك عادة وجبة الصباح الخاصة بك؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في الليل",
      "في الصباح في الصباح",
      "في المساء",
      "قبل أن يُسرر"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "في الصباح في الصباح",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you sleep?",
    "choices": [
      "Kitchen",
      "Classroom",
      "Bedroom",
      "Park"
    ],
    "answer": "Bedroom",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you sleep?",
      "What is your preferred sleeping spot?",
      "Where is your preferred spot for sleeping?",
      "Where is your preferred location for sleeping?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تنامين؟",
      "ما هو مكان النوم المفضل لديك؟",
      "إيهن مكان نومك المفضل؟",
      "إيهن موقع نومك المفضل؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "",
      "شيء",
      "غرفة النوم",
      "مُركْس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "غرفة النوم",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you wear when it’s raining?",
    "choices": [
      "Sunglasses",
      "Raincoat",
      "Shorts",
      "Swimsuit"
    ],
    "answer": "Raincoat",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "What do you wear when it’s raining?",
      "What clothing do you put on in the rain?",
      "What clothing do you usually wear when it rains?",
      "What clothing do you usually put on when it rains?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ماذا ترتدي عندما تمطر ؟",
      "ما هي الملابس اللي ترتديها في المطر؟",
      "ما هي الملابس اللي ترتديها عادة عندما تمطر؟",
      "ما هي الملابس اللي ترتديها عادة عندما تمطر؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "السنة",
      "المطر",
      "الشور",
      "سوي سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سو سوي"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "المطر",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When do you go to school?",
    "choices": [
      "Morning",
      "Midnight",
      "Evening",
      "Afternoon"
    ],
    "answer": "Morning",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "When do you go to school?",
      "When do you usually go to school?",
      "When do you typically go to school?",
      "At what time do you typically go to school?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "متى تذهب إلى المدرسة؟",
      "متى تذهبين عادة إلى المدرسة؟",
      "متى تذهبين عادة إلى المدرسة؟",
      "في إيه وقت تذهبين عادة إلى المدرسة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "صباحا صباحا",
      "منتصف النوم",
      "مُحْسِس",
      "ما بعد"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "صباحا صباحا",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you go to buy food?",
    "choices": [
      "Hospital",
      "Library",
      "Supermarket",
      "Cinema"
    ],
    "answer": "Supermarket",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you go to buy food?",
      "What is your go-to spot for purchasing food?",
      "What is your go-to location for buying food?",
      "What is your go-to spot for buying food?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تذهب لشراء الطعام؟",
      "ما هو موقعك لشراء الطعام؟",
      "ما هو موقعك لشراء الطعام؟",
      "ما هو موقعك لشراء الطعام؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "",
      "المكتبة",
      "",
      "ما"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What day comes after Monday?",
    "choices": [
      "Sunday",
      "Wednesday",
      "Tuesday",
      "Friday"
    ],
    "answer": "Tuesday",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "What day comes after Monday?",
      "What is the following day after Monday?",
      "What day follows Monday?",
      "What is the following day from Monday?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو اليوم الذي يأتي بعد يوم الاثنين؟",
      "ما هو التالي بعد يوم الاثنين؟",
      "ما هو اليوم الذي يليه يوم الاثنين؟",
      "ما هو اليوم التالي من يوم الاثنين؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الصبح",
      "الأربعاء الأربعاء",
      "يُنقل",
      "الجمعة الجمعة الجمعة الجمعة الجمعة الجمعة الجمعة الجمعة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "يُنقل",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you find books to read?",
    "choices": [
      "Gym",
      "Bakery",
      "Library",
      "Garden"
    ],
    "answer": "Library",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you find books to read?",
      "Where do you go to read books?",
      "What is your place to read books?",
      "What is your go-to spot for reading books?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تجد الكتب للقراءة؟",
      "إيهن تذهب لقراءة الكتب؟",
      "ما هو مكانك لقراءة الكتب؟",
      "ما هو موقعك لقراءة الكتب؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "",
      "الـمُرَجِز الـمُرَجِز",
      "المكتبة",
      ""
    ],
    "answer_ar": "المكتبة",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When do you say 'Good night'?",
    "choices": [
      "In the morning",
      "At lunch",
      "At night",
      "In class"
    ],
    "answer": "At night",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "When do you say 'Good night'?",
      "At what point do you greet someone with a \"Good night\"?",
      "At what point do you say 'Good night'?",
      "At what time do you greet someone with a \"Good night\"?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "متى تقول \"ليلة سعيدة\"؟",
      "في إيه مرحلة تحيين شخصاً بـ \"ليلة سعيدة\"؟",
      "في إيه نقطة تقول \"ليلة سعيدة\"؟",
      "في إيه وقت تحيي شخصاً بليلة سعيدة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في الصباح في الصباح",
      "الطعام",
      "في الليل",
      "في الدرجة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "في الليل",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you play football?",
    "choices": [
      "Bathroom",
      "Stadium",
      "Bedroom",
      "Kitchen"
    ],
    "answer": "Stadium",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you play football?",
      "What is the location of your football practice?",
      "What is your preferred location for football games?",
      "In what location do you typically watch football?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تلعب كرة القدم؟",
      "ما هو موقع تدريبك لكرة القدم؟",
      "ما هو موقعك المفضل لمباريات كرة القدم؟",
      "في إيه موقع تشاهد كرة القدم عادةً؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الحمامات",
      "الدورة الاستثنائية الأولى",
      "غرفة النوم",
      ""
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الدورة الاستثنائية الأولى",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What season is hot and sunny?",
    "choices": [
      "Winter",
      "Autumn",
      "Summer",
      "Spring"
    ],
    "answer": "Summer",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "What season is hot and sunny?",
      "At what time of the year is it most pleasant to be active and cool?",
      "At what time of the year do we experience the most sunny days?",
      "At what time of the year is it most pleasant to be warm and sunny?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الموسم الحار والمشمس؟",
      "في اي وقت من السنة يكون اكثر سرورا ان تكون نشيطا ورائعا ؟",
      "في اي وقت من السنة نختبر اكثر الايام مشمسة ؟",
      "في اي وقت من السنة يكون اكثر سرورا ان تكون دافئا ومشمسا ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "سكر",
      "الخريف",
      "الفرق",
      "سِرْس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الفرق",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you go to learn?",
    "choices": [
      "Zoo",
      "Mall",
      "School",
      "Beach"
    ],
    "answer": "School",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you go to learn?",
      "Where do you receive your academic education?",
      "What is your preferred location for studying?",
      "What is the location of your educational facility?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تذهب لتتعلم؟",
      "من إيهن تحصل على تعليمك الأكاديمي؟",
      "ما هو موقعك المفضل للدراسة ؟",
      "ما هو موقع مرفقك التعليمي؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "مُوجو",
      "المعامل",
      "المدرسة",
      "الشك"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "المدرسة",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What time do you go to bed?",
    "choices": [
      "Morning",
      "Evening",
      "Noon",
      "Afternoon"
    ],
    "answer": "Evening",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "What time do you go to bed?",
      "When do you go to sleep?",
      "When do you usually go to sleep?",
      "When do you usually go to bed?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "متى ستنام؟",
      "متى تنامين؟",
      "متى تنام عادةً؟",
      "متى تذهب عادة إلى السرير؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "صباحا صباحا",
      "مُحْسِس",
      "نونون",
      "ما بعد"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "مُحْسِس",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do airplanes take off?",
    "choices": [
      "Bus station",
      "Train station",
      "Airport",
      "Harbor"
    ],
    "answer": "Airport",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do airplanes take off?",
      "What is the starting point for airplanes?",
      "At what location do airplanes take off?",
      "Where do planes typically take off from during takeoff?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تقلع الطائرات؟",
      "ما هي نقطة انطلاق الطائرات؟",
      "في إيه موقع تقلع الطائرات؟",
      "من إيهن تقلع الطائرات عادةً أثناء الإقلاع؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "مهبط",
      "نقطة نقل",
      "طابور",
      "المرفرفر"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "طابور",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What day comes before Friday?",
    "choices": [
      "Monday",
      "Wednesday",
      "Thursday",
      "Saturday"
    ],
    "answer": "Thursday",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "What day comes before Friday?",
      "What is the day that precedes Friday?",
      "What is the day preceding Friday?",
      "What is the day before Friday?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه يوم يأتي قبل يوم الجمعة؟",
      "ما هو اليوم الذي يسبق يوم الجمعة؟",
      "ما هو اليوم السابق ليوم الجمعة؟",
      "ما هو اليوم قبل الجمعة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الاثنين الاثنين الاثنين الاثنين الاثنين",
      "الأربعاء الأربعاء",
      "واو خُفششش",
      "السبت"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "واو خُفششش",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When do you wear a coat?",
    "choices": [
      "In summer",
      "In winter",
      "At the beach",
      "While sleeping"
    ],
    "answer": "In winter",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "When do you wear a coat?",
      "What is the right time to wear a coat?",
      "What is the appropriate time to wear a coat?",
      "When do you put on a coat?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "متى ترتدي معطفاً؟",
      "ما هو الوقت المناسب لارتداء معطف؟",
      "ما هو الوقت المناسب لارتداء معطف؟",
      "متى ترتدي معطفاً؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في الصيف",
      ":: الشتاء",
      "على الشاطئ",
      "النوم أثناء النوم"
    ],
    "answer_ar": ":: الشتاء",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do doctors work?",
    "choices": [
      "Bank",
      "Hospital",
      "Restaurant",
      "Garage"
    ],
    "answer": "Hospital",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do doctors work?",
      "Where are doctors stationed to work?",
      "What is the work environment like for doctors?",
      "Where do medical professionals typically spend their time working?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن يعمل الأطباء؟",
      "اين يعمل الاطباء ؟",
      "كيف هي بيئة العمل بالنسبة للأطباء؟",
      "إيهن يقضي المهنيون الطبيون عادة وقتهم في العمل؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "مصرف",
      "",
      "محلات",
      ""
    ],
    "answer_ar": "",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you do in the afternoon?",
    "choices": [
      "Eat dinner",
      "Go to sleep",
      "Play or study",
      "Wake up"
    ],
    "answer": "Play or study",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "What do you do in the afternoon?",
      "How do you pass your time during the afternoon?",
      "How do you spend your afternoons?",
      "What activities do you engage in during the afternoon hours?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ماذا تفعل في فترة ما بعد الظهر؟",
      "كيف تمضي وقتك في فترة ما بعد الظهر؟",
      "كيف تقضي فترة ما بعد الظهر؟",
      "ما الأنشطة اللي تقوم بها خلال ساعات ما بعد الظهر؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الطعام",
      "الذهاب إلى النوم",
      "اللعب أو التعليم",
      "استيقظ استيقظ"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "اللعب أو التعليم",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you go to watch movies?",
    "choices": [
      "Theater",
      "Gym",
      "Bakery",
      "School"
    ],
    "answer": "Theater",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you go to watch movies?",
      "Where do you usually watch movies?",
      "What is your preferred movie-watching destination?",
      "What is your go-to spot for watching movies?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تذهب لمشاهدة الأفلام؟",
      "إيهن تشاهدين الأفلام عادة؟",
      "ما هي وجهتك المفضلة لمشاهدة الأفلام؟",
      "ما هو موقفك من مشاهدة الأفلام؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الحاضر",
      "",
      "الـمُرَجِز الـمُرَجِز",
      "المدرسة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الحاضر",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What comes after morning?",
    "choices": [
      "Evening",
      "Night",
      "Afternoon",
      "Midnight"
    ],
    "answer": "Afternoon",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "What comes after morning?",
      "What transpires after the end of the day?",
      "What follows the morning jolt?",
      "What follows the onset of daybreak?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما الذي يأتي بعد الصباح؟",
      "ما الذي يحدث بعد نهاية اليوم؟",
      "ما الذي يلي الحضّة الصباحية؟",
      "ما الذي يتبع بداية الفجر؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "مُحْسِس",
      "الصبح",
      "ما بعد",
      "منتصف النوم"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "ما بعد",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you keep your clothes?",
    "choices": [
      "Desk",
      "Closet",
      "Fridge",
      "Sink"
    ],
    "answer": "Closet",
    "category": "Time & Place",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you keep your clothes?",
      "Where is the storage location of your clothes?",
      "Where do you store your clothes?",
      "Where do you stash your clothes?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تحتفظ بملابسك؟",
      "إيهن مكان تخزين ملابسك؟",
      "إيهن تخزنين ملابسك؟",
      "إيهن خبأت ملابسك؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "المصب",
      "سرج",
      "المحتويات",
      "SS"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "سرج",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the cat in this sentence: 'The cat is under the table'?",
    "choices": [
      "On the table",
      "Next to the table",
      "Under the table",
      "Behind the table"
    ],
    "answer": "Under the table",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the cat in this sentence: 'The cat is under the table'?",
      "In the sentence \"The cat is under the table\", where exactly is the cat located?",
      "In the sentence \"The cat is under the table\", where is the cat located?",
      "Where can the cat be found in the sentence \"The cat is seated under the table\"?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن القطة في هذه الجُمله: القطة تحت الطاولة؟",
      "في الجُمله \"القط تحت الطاولة\" إيهن تقع القطة بالضبط؟",
      "في الجُمله \"القط تحت الطاولة\" إيهن تقع القطة؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على القطة في الجُمله \"القطة جالسة تحت الطاولة\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على الجدول",
      "التالي إلى الجدول",
      "تحت الجدول",
      "رابعاً - خلف الطاولة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "تحت الجدول",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'next to' mean?",
    "choices": [
      "Far away",
      "Very close",
      "On top",
      "Inside"
    ],
    "answer": "Very close",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "What does 'next to' mean?",
      "What is the meaning of 'next to'?",
      "Could you clarify the significance of 'next to'?",
      "Can you explain the definition of 'next to'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ماذا يعني \"التالي\" ؟",
      "ما معنى \"التالية\" ؟",
      "هل يمكنك أن توضح أهمية \"التالية\" ؟",
      "هل يمكنك شرح تعريف 'next to'؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "ألف - بُرّى",
      "قريب جدا جدا",
      "أعلى أعلى",
      "داخل"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "قريب جدا جدا",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the dog in: 'The dog is behind the sofa'?",
    "choices": [
      "In front of the sofa",
      "Behind the sofa",
      "Under the sofa",
      "On the sofa"
    ],
    "answer": "Behind the sofa",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the dog in: 'The dog is behind the sofa'?",
      "Where can the dog be found in 'The dog is situated behind the sofa'?",
      "Where can I find the dog in the passage titled 'The dog is situated behind the sofa'?",
      "In 'The dog is behind the sofa', where can I find the dog?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن هو الكلب في: \"الكلب وراء الأريكة\"؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على الكلب في 'الكلب يقع وراء الأريكة'؟",
      "إيهن يمكنني أن أجد الكلب في الممر تحت عنوان \"الكلب موجود خلف الأريكة\"؟",
      "في 'الكلب هو وراء الأريكة'، إيهن يمكنني العثور على الكلب؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "أمام مقدمة الصرّاف",
      "\"خلف القُرّة\"",
      "تحت النكهة",
      "على السكة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "\"خلف القُرّة\"",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the toy is inside the box, where is it?",
    "choices": [
      "On the box",
      "Next to the box",
      "Inside the box",
      "Behind the box"
    ],
    "answer": "Inside the box",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "If the toy is inside the box, where is it?",
      "In the box, where is the toy located?",
      "Where can I find the toy in the box?",
      "Where is the toy in the box if there is one?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كانت اللعبة داخل الصندوق، فإيهن هي؟",
      "في الصندوق، إيهن تقع اللعبة؟",
      "إيهن يمكنني أن أجد لعبة في الصندوق؟",
      "إيهن هي اللعبة في الصندوق إذا كان هناك واحدة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على الصندوق",
      "إلى التالي إلى مربع",
      "داخل الصندوق",
      "(الخلف وراء الصندوق"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "داخل الصندوق",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "What word tells you something is lower than another object?",
    "choices": [
      "Above",
      "Under",
      "Next to",
      "Behind"
    ],
    "answer": "Under",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "What word tells you something is lower than another object?",
      "What is the term used to describe something that is smaller than another thing?",
      "What is the term for indicating that something is situated below another thing?",
      "What term indicates that something is situated beneath another thing?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هي الكلمة اللي تخبرك أن شيئاً أقل من كائن آخر؟",
      "ما هو المصطلح المستخدم لوصف شيء أصغر من شيء آخر؟",
      "ما هو المصطلح للإشارة إلى أن شيئا ما يقع تحت شيء آخر؟",
      "ما هي العبارة اللي تشير الى ان شيئا ما يقع تحت شيء آخر ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "أولاً",
      "الموارد تحت",
      "إلى",
      "الخلف"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الموارد تحت",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is your nose?",
    "choices": [
      "On your hand",
      "On your arm",
      "On your face",
      "On your foot"
    ],
    "answer": "On your face",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is your nose?",
      "In what part of your anatomy does your nose end up?",
      "What is the location of your nose?",
      "What is the location of your nasal cavity?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن أنفك؟",
      "في إيه جزء من التشريح الخاص بك هل ينتهي أنفك؟",
      "ما هو موقع أنفك؟",
      "ما هو موقع تجويفك الأنفي؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على يدك على يدك",
      "على ذراعك",
      "على وجه وجهك",
      "على قدم قدمك"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "على وجه وجهك",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a ball is between two chairs, where is it?",
    "choices": [
      "On the chairs",
      "Outside the chairs",
      "Between the chairs",
      "Under the chairs"
    ],
    "answer": "Between the chairs",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "If a ball is between two chairs, where is it?",
      "Where can a ball be found if it is sandwiched between two chairs?",
      "Where can a ball be found if it is placed between two chairs?",
      "Where can we find a ball if it is between two chairs?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كانت الكرة بين كرسيين، إيهن هي؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على كرة إذا كانت مُسندة بين كرسيين؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على كرة إذا وضعت بين كرسيين؟",
      "إيهن يمكننا أن نجد كرة إذا كانت بين كرسيين؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على الكراسات",
      "خارج الكراسي",
      "بين الكراسات",
      "تحت الكراسات"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "بين الكراسات",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'above' mean?",
    "choices": [
      "Below",
      "Next to",
      "On top",
      "Inside"
    ],
    "answer": "On top",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "What does 'above' mean?",
      "What is the significance of 'above'?",
      "What is the definition of 'above'?",
      "What does 'above' signify?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ماذا يعني \"فوق\" ؟",
      "ما هي أهمية \"فوق\" ؟",
      "ما هو تعريف \"فوق\" ؟",
      "ماذا يعني \"فوق ده\" ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "ثانياً -",
      "إلى",
      "أعلى أعلى",
      "داخل"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "أعلى أعلى",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you sit in a classroom?",
    "choices": [
      "On the table",
      "On the chair",
      "Under the desk",
      "In the cupboard"
    ],
    "answer": "On the chair",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you sit in a classroom?",
      "What is your preferred seating position in a classroom?",
      "Where do you find yourself sitting in a classroom?",
      "Where do you find yourself in a classroom setting?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن تجلس في فصل دراسي؟",
      "ما هو موقع مقعدك المفضل في فصل دراسي؟",
      "إيهن تجد نفسك جالساً في فصل دراسي؟",
      "إيهن تجد نفسك في مكان فصل دراسي؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على الجدول",
      "على الكرسي",
      "تحت سطح المكتب",
      "في الخزانة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "على الكرسي",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the sun is in the sky, where is it?",
    "choices": [
      "Above you",
      "Next to you",
      "Behind you",
      "Under you"
    ],
    "answer": "Above you",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "If the sun is in the sky, where is it?",
      "Where is the sun, if it's in the sky?",
      "Where can the sun be found if it's in the sky?",
      "Where can we find the sun if it is in the sky?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كانت الشمس في السماء، فإيهن هي؟",
      "إيهن هي الشمس، إذا كانت في السماء؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على الشمس إذا كانت في السماء؟",
      "إيهن يمكننا أن نجد الشمس إذا كانت في السماء؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "فوقك",
      "إلى جانبك",
      "خلفك",
      "تحتك"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "فوقك",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the teacher usually standing?",
    "choices": [
      "Behind the students",
      "In front of the class",
      "Outside the school",
      "Next to the door"
    ],
    "answer": "In front of the class",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the teacher usually standing?",
      "What is the usual location of the teacher's desk?",
      "Where can I find the teacher's usual location?",
      "Where is the teacher usually found?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن يقف المعلم عادة؟",
      "ما هو الموقع المعتاد لمكتب المعلم؟",
      "إيهن يمكنني أن أجد مكان المعلم المعتاد؟",
      "إيهن يوجد المعلم عادة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الذي يُوَجّه الطّارف",
      "أمام الصف",
      "خارج المدرسة",
      "من خلال الباب"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "أمام الصف",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'inside' the pencil case?",
    "choices": [
      "The chair",
      "The pen",
      "The wall",
      "The book"
    ],
    "answer": "The pen",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "What is 'inside' the pencil case?",
      "What is contained within the inside of the pencil case?",
      "What is concealed within the pencil case?",
      "What is located inside the pencil case?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هي \"داخل\" حالة قلم الرصاص؟",
      "ماذا يوجد داخل داخل صندوق القلم؟",
      "ما الذي يُخفي داخل قضية القلم؟",
      "ماذا يوجد داخل صندوق قلم الرصاص؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "ألف - الكرسي",
      "القلم",
      "الجدار الجدار",
      "الكتاب الكتاب"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "القلم",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "If your friend is sitting 'beside' you, where is he?",
    "choices": [
      "In front of you",
      "Behind you",
      "Next to you",
      "Far from you"
    ],
    "answer": "Next to you",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "If your friend is sitting 'beside' you, where is he?",
      "Where is your friend when he sits next to you?",
      "If your friend is sitting next to you, where is he?",
      "If your friend is sitting with you, where is he?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كان صديقك يجلس \"بجانبك\" إيهن هو؟",
      "إيهن صديقك عندما يجلس بجانبك؟",
      "إذا كان صديقك يجلس بجانبك، إيهن هو؟",
      "إذا كان صديقك يجلس معك، إيهن هو؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في مقدمتك",
      "خلفك",
      "إلى جانبك",
      "من بعيد عنك"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "إلى جانبك",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'behind' mean?",
    "choices": [
      "In front",
      "At the back",
      "Next to",
      "Inside"
    ],
    "answer": "At the back",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "What does 'behind' mean?",
      "What does the word 'behind' signify?",
      "What is the definition of 'behind'?",
      "What does the term 'behind' signify?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ماذا تعني \"خلفية\" ؟",
      "ما معنى كلمة \"خلفية\"؟",
      "ما هو تعريف \"الخلفية\"؟",
      "ماذا يعني مصطلح \"ما وراء\" ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في المقدمة",
      "في الجزء الخلفي",
      "إلى",
      "داخل"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "في الجزء الخلفي",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the ball in: 'The ball is on the shelf'?",
    "choices": [
      "On the floor",
      "In the box",
      "On the shelf",
      "Next to the box"
    ],
    "answer": "On the shelf",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the ball in: 'The ball is on the shelf'?",
      "Where can the ball be found when someone says 'The ball is on the shelf'?",
      "Where can the ball be found in the phrase 'The ball is on the shelf'?",
      "Where can the ball be found when someone says 'the ball is on the shelf'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن الكرة في: \"الكرة على الرف\"؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على الكرة عندما يقول أحدهم \"الكرة على الرف\"؟",
      "إيهن يمكن أن توجد الكرة في عبارة \"الكرة على الرف\"؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على الكرة عندما يقول شخص ما 'الكرة على الرف'؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على الأرض",
      "في الصندوق",
      "على الرف",
      "إلى التالي إلى مربع"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "على الرف",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the opposite of 'above'?",
    "choices": [
      "On",
      "Inside",
      "Under",
      "Next to"
    ],
    "answer": "Under",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "What’s the opposite of 'above'?",
      "What is the antonym of 'above'?",
      "What is the reverse of 'above'?",
      "What is the contrary of 'above'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو عكس \"أعلى\" ؟",
      "ما هو اسم \"أعلى\" ؟",
      "ما هو العكس من 'أعلى'؟",
      "ما هو نقيض \"فوق\" ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "& من طراز",
      "داخل",
      "الموارد تحت",
      "إلى"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الموارد تحت",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the box is in front of the boy, where is the boy?",
    "choices": [
      "Behind the box",
      "Inside the box",
      "On top of the box",
      "Next to the box"
    ],
    "answer": "Behind the box",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "If the box is in front of the boy, where is the boy?",
      "In the box, where is the boy located if he is standing?",
      "Where is the boy if he is in front of the box?",
      "In the box, where is the boy located if he is in front of it?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كان الصندوق أمام الصبي، إيهن الصبي؟",
      "في الصندوق، إيهن يقع الفتى إن كان واقفاً؟",
      "إيهن الصبي إذا كان أمام الصندوق؟",
      "في الصندوق، إيهن هو مكان الصبي إذا كان أمامه؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "(الخلف وراء الصندوق",
      "داخل الصندوق",
      "على أعلى الصندوق",
      "إلى التالي إلى مربع"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "(الخلف وراء الصندوق",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you put your shoes?",
    "choices": [
      "On your head",
      "On your feet",
      "On your hands",
      "On the table"
    ],
    "answer": "On your feet",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where do you put your shoes?",
      "What is the proper placement for your shoes?",
      "Where do you store your shoes?",
      "What is the correct placement for your shoes?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن وضعت حذائك؟",
      "ما هو المكان المناسب لحذائك؟",
      "إيهن تخزن حذائك؟",
      "ما هو المكان الصحيح لحذائك؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على رأسك على رأسك",
      "في أرجلك",
      "على إيهدي إيهديك",
      "على الجدول"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "في أرجلك",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the kitchen in most houses?",
    "choices": [
      "In the garden",
      "In the garage",
      "Inside the house",
      "On the roof"
    ],
    "answer": "Inside the house",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the kitchen in most houses?",
      "In what part of a home can the kitchen be found?",
      "Where can one find the majority of the houses equipped with a kitchen?",
      "What is the typical location of the kitchen in a household?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن المطبخ في معظم المنازل؟",
      "في إيه جزء من المنزل يمكن أن يوجد المطبخ؟",
      "إيهن يمكن للمرء أن يجد غالبية المنازل مجهزة بمطبخ؟",
      "ما هو الموقع النموذجي للمطبخ في البيت ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في الجنة : في الجنة في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة : في الجنة",
      "في المرآب",
      "داخل المنزل",
      "على السقف"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "داخل المنزل",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the clock usually placed in a classroom?",
    "choices": [
      "On the floor",
      "Under the table",
      "On the wall",
      "In the drawer"
    ],
    "answer": "On the wall",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the clock usually placed in a classroom?",
      "In what area of a classroom is the clock usually located?",
      "Where is the clock in a classroom?",
      "What is the typical placement of the clock in a classroom?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن يتم وضع الساعة عادة في فصل دراسي؟",
      "في ايّ منطقة في الصف تقع الساعة عادة ؟",
      "إيهن الساعة في فصل دراسي؟",
      "ما هو وضع الساعة النموذجي في فصل دراسي؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على الأرض",
      "تحت الجدول",
      "على الجدار الجدار :",
      "في الدرج"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "على الجدار الجدار :",
    "category_ar": "درجة الوعي"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which direction do you turn if you move to your right?",
    "choices": [
      "Left",
      "Right",
      "Up",
      "Down"
    ],
    "answer": "Right",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "Which direction do you turn if you move to your right?",
      "What is the direction of movement when you move towards the right?",
      "What is the direction of movement when you shift to the right?",
      "What is the direction of movement if you move to the right?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إلى إيه اتجاه ستتحول إذا تحركت إلى اليمين؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه الحركة عندما تتحرك نحو اليمين؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه الحركة عندما تتحول إلى اليمين؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه الحركة إذا تحركت إلى اليمين؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "يمين يمين",
      "Uup",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م أ م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "يمين يمين",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "If you are facing north and turn left, what direction are you facing now?",
    "choices": [
      "East",
      "South",
      "West",
      "North"
    ],
    "answer": "West",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If you are facing north and turn left, what direction are you facing now?",
      "If you turn left and face north, what direction will you face?",
      "If you turn left and face north, what is the direction you're going?",
      "If you turn left facing north, what is the direction you're going?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كنت تواجه الشمال وتستدير يسارا، ما الاتجاه الذي تواجهه الآن؟",
      "إذا استدرت يساراً وواجهت شمالاً، ما الاتجاه الذي ستواجهه؟",
      "إذا استدرت يساراً وواجهت شمالاً، ما هو الاتجاه الذي تسير فيه؟",
      "إذا اتجهت يساراً باتجاه الشمال، ما هو الاتجاه الذي تسير فيه؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "باء - المسائل المتعلقة",
      "جنوب جنوب جنوب",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)",
      "شمالي"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which direction is opposite to up?",
    "choices": [
      "Down",
      "Left",
      "Right",
      "Behind"
    ],
    "answer": "Down",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "Which direction is opposite to up?",
      "What is the opposite direction of up?",
      "What is the direction opposite to up?",
      "What is the direction of the sun's gravitational pull towards up?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه اتجاه هو العكس إلى أعلى؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه المقابل للارتفاع؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه العكسي إلى أعلى؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه جاذبية الشمس نحو الأعلى؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م أ م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "يمين يمين",
      "الخلف"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م أ م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "If you walk backward, where are you going?",
    "choices": [
      "Forward",
      "Back",
      "Up",
      "Right"
    ],
    "answer": "Back",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If you walk backward, where are you going?",
      "If you walk backwards, where do you intend to go?",
      "If you were to walk in the opposite direction, where would you go?",
      "What is the destination if you reverse your walking?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كنت تسير إلى الوراء، إلى إيهن أنت ذاهب؟",
      "إذا كنت تسير إلى الوراء، إيهن تنوي أن تذهب؟",
      "إذا كنت تسير في الاتجاه المعاكس، إيهن ستذهب؟",
      "ما هي الوجهة إذا عكست مسارك؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "قِدم",
      "& حرّر",
      "Uup",
      "يمين يمين"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "& حرّر",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What direction is opposite to right?",
    "choices": [
      "Up",
      "Down",
      "Left",
      "Back"
    ],
    "answer": "Left",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "What direction is opposite to right?",
      "What is the direction that is opposite to the right?",
      "Which direction is in the opposite direction?",
      "What is the opposite direction to the right?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الاتجاه المعاكس لليمين؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه المقابل لليمين؟",
      "إيه اتجاه هو في الاتجاه المعاكس؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه المعاكس لليمين؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "Uup",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م أ م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "& حرّر"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "If the ball is in front of the box, where is the box?",
    "choices": [
      "Behind the ball",
      "In front of the ball",
      "Next to the ball",
      "Above the ball"
    ],
    "answer": "Behind the ball",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If the ball is in front of the box, where is the box?",
      "Where can the ball be found if it is in front of the box?",
      "If the ball is in front of the box, where is the box located?",
      "Where can the ball be found if it is placed in front of the box?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كانت الكرة أمام الصندوق، إيهن الصندوق؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على الكرة إذا كانت أمام الصندوق؟",
      "إذا كانت الكرة أمام الصندوق، فإيهن يقع الصندوق؟",
      "إيهن يمكن العثور على الكرة إذا كانت توضع أمام الصندوق؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "أولاً - الأساس",
      "أمام أمام الكرة",
      "التالي إلى الكرة",
      "فوق الكرة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "أولاً - الأساس",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What direction do you look to see the ceiling?",
    "choices": [
      "Down",
      "Left",
      "Up",
      "Back"
    ],
    "answer": "Up",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "What direction do you look to see the ceiling?",
      "Which direction do you tend to look at in order to see the ceiling?",
      "What direction do you tend to take to see the ceiling?",
      "Which direction do you tend to look towards to see the top of the sky?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما الاتجاه الذي تنظر إليه لترى السقف؟",
      "ما الاتجاه الذي تميل إلى النظر إليه لرؤية السقف؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه الذي تميل إلى اتخاذه لرؤية السقف؟",
      "ما الاتجاه الذي تميل إلى النظر نحو رؤية قمة السماء؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م أ م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "Uup",
      "& حرّر"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "Uup",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "If a person is standing behind you, where are they?",
    "choices": [
      "In front of you",
      "Next to you",
      "Behind you",
      "Above you"
    ],
    "answer": "Behind you",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If a person is standing behind you, where are they?",
      "Where is the person standing in your way?",
      "If someone is behind you, where is the person?",
      "If someone is behind you, where can they be found?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كان هناك شخص يقف خلفك، إيهن هم؟",
      "إيهن الشخص الذي يقف في طريقك؟",
      "إذا كان هناك شخص خلفك إيهن الشخص؟",
      "إن كان هناك شخص خلفك فإيهن يمكن العثور عليه؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في مقدمتك",
      "إلى جانبك",
      "خلفك",
      "فوقك"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "خلفك",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which direction does the sun rise from?",
    "choices": [
      "North",
      "South",
      "East",
      "West"
    ],
    "answer": "East",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "Which direction does the sun rise from?",
      "What is the direction of the sun's rising?",
      "From where does the sun rise?",
      "Which direction does the sun rise in?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "من إيه اتجاه تشرق الشمس؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه شروق الشمس؟",
      "من إيهن تشرق الشمس؟",
      "في إيه اتجاه تشرق الشمس؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "شمالي",
      "جنوب جنوب جنوب",
      "باء - المسائل المتعلقة",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "باء - المسائل المتعلقة",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which way do you move to go downstairs?",
    "choices": [
      "Up",
      "Down",
      "Left",
      "Right"
    ],
    "answer": "Down",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "Which way do you move to go downstairs?",
      "What is your method for going down the hall?",
      "What is the way to go down the stairs?",
      "How do you go down the stairs?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "من إيه طريق ستنتقلين للذهاب إلى الأسفل؟",
      "ما هي طريقتك للذهاب إلى أسفل القاعة؟",
      "ما هي طريقة النزول من السلالم؟",
      "كيف تنزل الدرج؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "Uup",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م أ م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "يمين يمين"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م أ م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "If your right hand is raised, which side is it?",
    "choices": [
      "Left",
      "Right",
      "Top",
      "Back"
    ],
    "answer": "Right",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If your right hand is raised, which side is it?",
      "If you have a raised right hand, which side do you stand?",
      "If you have a raised right hand, which side do you stand on?",
      "Which side of your hand does the raised right hand belong to?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "اذا رفعت يدك اليمنى اي جانب هو؟",
      "اذا كان لديك يد يمينية مرفوعة اي جانب تقف؟",
      "اذا كان لديك يد يمينية مرفوعة اي جانب تقف عليه ؟",
      "إلى إيه جانب من يدك تعمل اليد اليمنى؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "يمين يمين",
      "أعلى",
      "& حرّر"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "يمين يمين",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What direction do you face if you turn around completely?",
    "choices": [
      "Same as before",
      "Opposite direction",
      "Right",
      "Left"
    ],
    "answer": "Opposite direction",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "What direction do you face if you turn around completely?",
      "When you turn around, what is the direction you turn towards?",
      "What is the direction you turn towards when you turn completely?",
      "What is the direction you turn to when you turn around entirely?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الاتجاه الذي ستواجهه إذا استدرت بالكامل؟",
      "عندما تستدير، ما هو الاتجاه الذي تتجه نحوه؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه الذي تتجه نحوه عندما تتحول تماما؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه الذي تتحول إليه عندما تستدير كلياً؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "نفس الأمر في الفترة",
      "الاتجاه المعاكس",
      "يمين يمين",
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الاتجاه المعاكس",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which direction is between north and east?",
    "choices": [
      "Northeast",
      "South",
      "West",
      "Southeast"
    ],
    "answer": "Northeast",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "Which direction is between north and east?",
      "What is the direction of the line that runs from north to east?",
      "What is the direction of travel from north to east?",
      "What is the direction of movement from north to east?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الاتجاه بين الشمال والشرق؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه الخط الذي يمتد من الشمال إلى الشرق؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه السفر من الشمال إلى الشرق؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه الحركة من الشمال إلى الشرق؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الشمالية الشرقية",
      "جنوب جنوب جنوب",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)",
      "جنوب جنوب جنوب جنوب جنوب"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "الشمالية الشرقية",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "If you move to your left and then go down, where are you going?",
    "choices": [
      "Up",
      "Forward",
      "Left and down",
      "Right"
    ],
    "answer": "Left and down",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If you move to your left and then go down, where are you going?",
      "What is the destination if you move leftward and then start descending?",
      "If you move left, and then go down, where do you go next?",
      "What is the destination if you move leftward and then begin to descend?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا تحركت إلى يسارك ثم سقطت إلى إيهن أنت ذاهب؟",
      "ما هي الوجهة إذا تحركت يساراً ثم بدأت بالهبوط؟",
      "إن تحركت يساراً ثم نزلت إلى الأسفل، فإيهن ستذهب بعد ده؟",
      "ما هي الوجهة إذا تحركت يسارا ثم بدأت بالهبوط؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "Uup",
      "قِدم",
      "مُسَكَّل و أسفل",
      "يمين يمين"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "مُسَكَّل و أسفل",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which direction is opposite to forward?",
    "choices": [
      "Right",
      "Left",
      "Backward",
      "Up"
    ],
    "answer": "Backward",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "Which direction is opposite to forward?",
      "What is the opposite direction of the forward direction?",
      "What is the opposite direction of forward motion?",
      "What is the opposite axis to the forward motion?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه اتجاه هو عكس الاتجاه إلى الأمام؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه المعاكس للاتجاه إلى الأمام؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه المعاكس للتحرك للأمام؟",
      "ما هو المحور المقابل للحركة الأمامية؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "يمين يمين",
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "إلى الخلف",
      "Uup"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "إلى الخلف",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What direction do you take to open a door inwards?",
    "choices": [
      "Push",
      "Pull",
      "Turn right",
      "Turn left"
    ],
    "answer": "Push",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "What direction do you take to open a door inwards?",
      "What is the orientation of a door when it is opened inwards?",
      "What is the orientation of a door when it is opened inwardly?",
      "In which direction do you open a door?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الاتجاه الذي تأخذه لفتح باب إلى الداخل؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه الباب عندما يفتح إلى الداخل؟",
      "ما هو اتجاه الباب عندما يفتح داخله؟",
      "في إيه اتجاه تفتحين الباب؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 م و، 1 م أ م",
      "رقم الهاتف:",
      "يمين",
      "اندور يسار"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 م و، 1 م أ م",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "If you're facing east and turn right, where are you facing?",
    "choices": [
      "South",
      "North",
      "West",
      "East"
    ],
    "answer": "South",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If you're facing east and turn right, where are you facing?",
      "If you turn right and face east, where do you see?",
      "If you turn right and face east, where do you currently stand?",
      "When you turn right and face east, where is the destination?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إذا كنت تواجه الشرق وتنعطف يميناً، فإيهن تواجه؟",
      "إذا انعطفت يميناً وواجهت شرقاً إيهن ترى؟",
      "إذا انعطفت يميناً وواجهت شرقاً، إيهن تقف حالياً؟",
      "عندما تنعطف يميناً وتتجه شرقاً، إيهن الوجهة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "جنوب جنوب جنوب",
      "شمالي",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)",
      "باء - المسائل المتعلقة"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "جنوب جنوب جنوب",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the moon usually seen at night?",
    "choices": [
      "Below",
      "Up",
      "Left",
      "Next to the sun"
    ],
    "answer": "Up",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the moon usually seen at night?",
      "What is the usual place to view the moon during nighttime?",
      "What is the usual place to view the moon?",
      "What is the usual place to observe the moon at night?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيهن يُرى القمر عادة في الليل؟",
      "ما هو المكان المعتاد لرؤية القمر أثناء الليل؟",
      "ما هو المكان المعتاد لرؤية القمر؟",
      "ما هو المكان المعتاد لمراقبة القمر في الليل؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "ثانياً -",
      "Uup",
      "1 ف-5، 1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م و، 1 م",
      "تال للشمس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "Uup",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What direction is the opposite of north?",
    "choices": [
      "East",
      "West",
      "South",
      "Northeast"
    ],
    "answer": "South",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "What direction is the opposite of north?",
      "What is the reverse of north?",
      "What is the polar opposite of north?",
      "What is the lateral direction of north and south?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "ما هو الاتجاه المقابل للشمال؟",
      "ما هو عكس اتجاه الشمال؟",
      "ما هو القطب المقابل للشمال؟",
      "ما هو الاتجاه الجانبي للشمال والجنوب؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "باء - المسائل المتعلقة",
      "1 ف-4، 1 ف-3، 1 خ م، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)، 1 خ ع (رأ)",
      "جنوب جنوب جنوب",
      "الشمالية الشرقية"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "جنوب جنوب جنوب",
    "category_ar": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which side is your left hand on?",
    "choices": [
      "Right side",
      "Back",
      "Front",
      "Left side"
    ],
    "answer": "Left side",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "Which side is your left hand on?",
      "What is the position of your left hand?",
      "What is the location of your left hand?",
      "What is the location of the left hand's position?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "إيه جانب هو يدك اليسرى على؟",
      "ما هو موقف يدك اليسرى؟",
      "ما هو موقع يدك اليسرى؟",
      "ما هو موقع موقع اليد اليسرى؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "",
      "& حرّر",
      "الفئة الفنية",
      ""
    ],
    "answer_ar": "",
    "category_ar": ""
  }
]